(阿巴拉契亚山脉单车径  温泉地区)
你刚刚差点没跟上我
You almost lost me back there.
- 那么 这是什么地方 - 特别的地方
- So, what is this place? - Someplace special.
我还是小孩时有一次跟家里人 露营发现了这个地方
I found this on a family camping trip when I was a kid.
进来啊
Go on in.
真的假的
Are you serious?
水是温的
It's warm.
当然了 这是温泉啊 你这个呆瓜
Of course. They're hot springs, you goof.
喔 水还有点热
Whoo! It's hot!
喔…
Ooh...
这足够吗
Is this enough?
好吧 如果你真的想 回归自然…
Well, if you really wanna go back to nature...
- 热热的真舒服 - 答应我 我们每年都泡泡温泉
- It's nice and hot. - Promise we'll do this every year.
直到年华老去
Until we wrinkle.
喔
Whoo!
尼克
Nick?
亲爱的 你受伤了吗
Sweetie, are you hurt?
达里亚 啊
Daria! Ah!
我在这儿 啊
Over here! Ah!
尼克
Nick!
你没事吧
Are you OK?
- 你摔倒了 - 没有 有人他妈的射了我
- Did you fall? - No. Someone fucking shot me.
什么
What?
啊
Ahh!
《致命弯道6：终极审判》
那你就一点儿不知道
So you had no idea?
他是被收养的 你知道的
He's adopted, you know that.
谢谢 托妮 只是从大一才开始认识他
Thanks, Toni, having only known him since freshman year.
不过还是挺酷的 是不
Still kind of cool, though, right?
发现你 其实还有家人
Finding out you actually had some family out there.
我们是他家人 不然我们怎么会过来
We are his family. That's why we're all here.
这也是我哥和那些人会 跟在我们后面一起来的原因
And that's why my brother and those guys are right behind us.
听着 我不知道此行会遇到什么
Look, I don't know what to expect.
我不认识这些人 也没来过这地方
I don't know these people or this place.
也许我将要继承莫泰6
I could be inheriting a Motel 6.
又或… 一个毒枭集团
Or... a meth empire.
我只是说说 这是阿巴拉契亚山脉啊
I'm just saying, it's the Appalachians.
我谢谢你 维克
Thanks, Vic.
如果我可以帮到你的话 我做了些调查
If it'll help, I did some digging.
- 你又不用这个写专栏 - 当然不用
- This isn't for one of your columns. - Of course not.
我只喜欢调查研究
I'm just the investigative type.
霍布温泉庄园 被某个未知家族于1926年建立
Hobb Springs, established 1926 by families unknown.
也许是你的家族
Maybe yours.
美国第一所位于巴特尔克里 郊外的疗养院
The first sanitarium in America outside Battle Creek.
嗯 大多数人会同意吧
Well, most people would approve.
- 同意什么 - 我去疗养院
- Of what? - Me going into a sanitarium.
(霍布温泉庄园  始于1902年)
艾格尼丝 菲尔兹
Agnes Fields.
- 你得用自己的 - 就这么说定了 杰克森先生
- You are gonna get yours. - I'll hold you to that, Mr. Jackson.
更像一个养生矿泉疗养院 真的
It's more like a health spa, really.
疗养院不会建户外厕所 布莱恩
Spas don't come with their own outhouse, Bryan.
喜莉安 就两周 好吧
Jillian, it's two weeks, OK?
你知道 把丹尼弄到户外
You know, getting Danny out in the open air,
看看这个继承物到底怎样
seeing how much of an inheritance this really is.
真的吗 罗德 我修轮胎就这么让人惊奇
Really, Rod? Me fixing a tire is so amazing?
- 我只是试试我的新摄像机 - 是啊
- Just playing with my new camera. - Yeah.
上次旅行你用你的旧摄像机 把我的裸照晒得全网都是
And your old camera posted my naked ass all over the internet last trip!
你一天点击量就是4000啊
And got 4,000 hits in one day.
再者说了 这也挺有趣
Besides, come on, it's fun.
愉快是我们都需要的治疗方式
And fun is just the kind of therapy we all need.
- 特别是我妹妹和丹尼 - 是啊
- Especially my sister and Danny. - Yeah.
我爱愉快疗法
Gotta love therapy.
想开始康复进程吗
Wanna start the healing process?
萨莉
Sally?
你今早晨照了6次镜子了
You've checked yourself six times this morning.
- 他很快会来 - 我知道
- He'll be here real soon. - I know.
还得一会呢
It may take some time.
我过不了另一个冬天了
I can't go another winter.
我需要这个
I need this.
我们都需要
We need this.
我们尽量争取
We play this right,
妹妹 他抗拒不了你的
sister, he won't be able to resist you.
上帝知道我抗拒不了
Lord knows I can't.
伙计们 这简直巨大啊
You guys, it's gigantic.
- 你继承了这个 - 我想是吧
- You inherited this? - I guess so.
这个国家的一个小地方
Our little place in the country.
嗯 这可不是莫泰6
Well, it ain't a Motel 6.
刷几层漆的话 就是…
Couple coats of paint, and it could be...
他妈的太雄伟了
Fucking brilliant.
有点吓人
Creepy.
维克 下车
Vic, get out of the car.
我要跟我男朋友单独呆会
I need a moment alone with my boyfriend.
好吧
Fine.
该决定了
It's time to decide.
想怎么做
What do you want to do?
正当我的人生陷入 最低谷的时候
Just when I hit the lowest I've ever hit,
我收到一封信 信上说我属于某种东西
I got a letter saying that I belonged to something.
我几年前放弃的东西
Something that I gave up on years ago.
告诉我你想怎么做 亲爱的
Tell me what you wanna do, honey.
我想见见这些人 了解关于我的事情
I wanna meet these people and find out what I'm all about.
哦 老天呐
Oh, my God.
- 是啊 - 哇喔
- Yeah. - Wow.
- 太宏伟了 - 我知道 是不是
- It's huge. - I know, right?
欢迎来到霍布温泉庄园
Welcome to Hobb Springs.
- 丹尼 - 是我 是的
- Danny. - That's right, yeah.
我看你的眼睛就知道是你
I could tell by your eyes.
真不敢相信你可算来了
I cannot believe that you are finally here.
- 你哪位 - 这应该是萨莉
- And who are you? - This would be Sally.
我叫杰克森 我们是管理员
I'm Jackson. We're the caretakers here.
我们不知道你朋友会来 不过 呃…
We weren't expecting your friends, but, um...
不过我确定我们可以接待你们
...I'm pretty sure we can handle you, though.
哦 我们只是第一波
Oh, we're just the first wave.
这地方简直太大了
This is huge!
我们不会迷路吧
How are we even gonna find our way around in there?
他们管这叫温泉疗养院
They call this a spa?
最好撒点面包屑做记号
Better leave a trail of breadcrumbs.
我们轮胎破了
We got a flat,
- 然后有点… - 醉了
- and then got a little... - Baked.
绕圈了
Turned around.
知道了 没问题 我们房间很多
I see, no problem. We have plenty of vacancies coming up.
别但心 他们今天就退房 然后这地方就
Don't worry, they'll be checking out today and then we'll have the place
- 都是我的了 - 哦 很好
- all to ourselves. - Oh, goody.
很乐意带你们到处转转
I'd be happy to show you around.
啊 要不我们先把包拿进去吧
Uh, maybe we could get our bags first.
是啊 也许该分房间了 旅途疲惫啊
Yeah, maybe some rooms. It's been a long drive.
你们想怎样都行 我们现在为你们工作
Whatever you wish. We work for you now.
真不错
That's pretty cool, actually.
- 丹尼现在有仆人了 - 嘿 你好吗
- Danny has servants now? - Hey, how you doing?
都进来吧
Ya'll come on in.
谢谢
Thank you.
天呐
Geez.
作为乡下人来说他们相当漂亮
They're kind of good-looking for hillbillies.
他们是表兄妹 不是 哥哥和妹妹
They're cousins. No, brother and sister.
一样的
Same thing around these parts.
得了 他们也许只是普通夫妇
Come on, they're probably just a normal couple.
- 他们长得挺逗的 - 像阿米希人
- They're funny-looking. - And Amish.
实际上
Actually,
我们是在我们的贵格会
we're kissing cousins on
兄弟姐妹那边可以接吻的表兄妹
our Quaker brother's sister's side.
真对不起 我们失礼了
I'm so sorry, that was so rude of us.
我们的风言风语以前也有不少
Ain't nothing we haven't heard before.
现在我就不当回事了
Just let it roll off my back nowadays.
你们真的是兄妹
So you really are brother and sister?
如我所说 我们没想到会来这么多人
As I said, we weren't expecting so many.
想吃的话 我们再做点
We can make more, if you'd like.
啊 不 不 没关系 真的
Uh, no, no, it's fine. Really.
你们在这休息一下 我们想想
We'll leave you here to rest a spell while we figure out
怎样最好地服务你们
how best to deal with you.
那是什么哦
What is that?
坐吧 坐下
Go on, sit down.
- 我们真要呆在这里 - 怎么了 有什么不妥吗
- We're really staying here? - Why, what's wrong?
这一切无疑透着古怪
Ain't no doubt all of this is a little bit weird.
- 对 - 你们没觉得
- Yeah. - You guys don't get
这地方挺有吸引力的吗
the charm of this place?
我觉得也是
I do.
你拆了这里 细分这片土地
You rip the place down, subdivide the land,
然后我们回来 我们会请某人 过来做个真正的保价
and we go back, we'll send someone in for a real appraisal.
是啊 我想你忘了我没地方可去
Yeah, I think you're forgetting that I don't have anywhere to go.
什么 那么这就是你家喽
What, so this is your home now?
不知道 也许吧
I don't know. Maybe.
丹尼 你过去混中央公园的
Danny, you're used to Central Park West
- 周五晚上都是随叫随到 - 是啊 看看我的下场吧
- and Nobu on Friday nights. - Yeah. And look what that did to me.
嘿 我们不需要现在就做决定 没关系的
Hey, we don't have to make a decision right away. It's fine.
这地方是有生命的 有它的历史 隐秘
This place is alive. It has history, secrets.
至少两个星期会不断给我们惊喜
Enough excitement for two weeks at least.
- 维克 支持我一下 - 呃 当然
- Come on, back me up, Vic. - Uh, sure.
这样有年代的地方 一定有它自己的标志
A place this old surely has a book in it.
- 也许说不定还被用作电影素材呢 - 除了谋杀
- Maybe a movie even. - Short of murder,
或者某个好莱坞丑闻 谁在意呢
or a Hollywood scandal, who'd give a shit?
我在意啊 布莱恩 我们可能正在讨论我的家族史
Me, Bryan. We could be talking about my history.
- 所以我同意留下 - 好 我也留下
- So me. - Yeah, me too.
- 我留下 - 得忠于家庭
- Me. - Gotta stick by family.
是我摇铃叫的那个高高的 强壮男人吗
Is that the big, strong man I rang for?
这才像话
That's more like it.
喂
Hello?
杰克森先生
Mr. Jackson?
喂 哦…
Hello?! Oh...
嘘…
Shhh...
愚蠢的老太婆
Silly little bitty.
控制点自己 伙计们 这是我的唯一要求
A little self control, boys! That's all I ask!
哦 我的天 这是真的金子吗
Oh, my God! Is that real gold?
哦 布莱恩 赫普怀特纯手工家具
Oh, Bryan! These are Hepplewhite!
那些不看古董路演的人
And for those that don't watch Antique Roadshow...
哦 保存得真好
Oh, and they look to be in perfect condition.
- 哦 有它们的价值难以值量 - 难以估量
- Oh, they're gonna be worth a fortune. - A fortune?
现在你觉得我的家怎样啊 布莱恩
How'd you like my place now, Bryan?
嘿 伙计们 这地方好多了
Hey, guys. This place just got a whole lot better.
- 什么 - 哦 好么
- What? - Oh, great.
他去哪
Where's he going now?
我们脱了吧
Let's get naked.
喔
Whoo!
这里闻着真香
It actually smells sweet.
嘿 伙计们 我们要泡就要有点风格
Hey, guys, if we're gonna do this, we're gonna do this in style.
- 你们准备好了吗 - 别
- You ready for it? - No!
- 多谢啊 老兄 - 进来啊
- Thanks, man. - Come on in!
这地方够大
There's room for everybody!
- 嘿 你没事吧 - 这些真的都是我的
- Hey. You OK? - It's really all mine.
我还没想明白
I'm still wrapping my head around that.
也许我们需要这些
Maybe it's just what we needed.
我想我们得在这里将就了
I suppose this will have to do.
恐怕这是我们仅有的寝室了
Afraid this is all we have right now.
不是吧 我们是这位新房主的朋友
Hello? We're the new owner's best friends.
所以你可以安排得更好点
So you can do better.
都到了吧
Are we all here?
你们玩那些骑车的人玩得很高兴
Now, you boys had your fun with those bikers.
你们也摧残了那小姑娘了
And you messed with the little bitty real nice.
停下吧
Now quit!
别碰丹尼 即是这意味着也不能碰他的朋友
Leave Danny alone. Even if it means giving his friends a pass.
我觉得我说得很明白了
Now I thought I made myself clear!
不会等很久的 你们可以尽情围猎他们
It won't be long, and you can all have at 'em as much as you like.
如果你们还这么做的话
Now you keep doing
你们会毁了我们所有人要的东西
what you're doing you're gonna ruin this for all of us!
我说得够明白了吗 明白了没有
Do I make myself clear? Do you understand me?
操蛋的家族
Fucking family.
那你要怎么用这个摄像机 老兄
So, like, what's the plan with the cameras, dude?
你走哪都带着
Like, you're carrying them around everywhere.
是啊 老兄 看 小巧易隐藏
Yeah, man. Look. Compact and easy to hide.
我觉得我们应该把这个放在丹尼的房间里
I think we should put one of these in Danny's room.
哦 我可不能去看我姐姐的裸照 但还是要感谢你
Oh, I'm not up for seeing my sister naked, but thank you, though.
那么拍我们怎么样 老兄
Well, what about the rest of us, dude?
你这贱货
Fucking asshole!
丹尼
Danny.
哦 该死
Oh, shit.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
请告诉我你把这个拍下来了
Please tell me you got a camera for this.
给我 给我
Give it here, give it here.
我要感谢学院授予我的崇高奖励
I'd like to thank the Academy for this prestigious award.
我会每天享用它
I will enjoy this every single day.
你说让我们掏钱来采购 公平何在
Tell me how it's fair that we have to pay for groceries.
啊…
Aw...
可怜的小狗
Poor puppy!
- 布莱恩 - 什么事
- Bryan. - Yeah?
来看看这个
Come check this out.
你们只是路过
You folks just passing through?
不 我们住在霍布温泉庄园
No, we're staying up at Hobb Springs.
不用说了
You don't say.
我自己可不想再去那里了 但我想又快要去了
I don't get up there much myself anymore, but I expect I will be.
- 嗯 为什么 - 你们刚住进去
- Well, why is that? - You just got in?
- 是的 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你们看到一群老女人在那欢腾吗
You all see a bunch of little, old ladies be-bopping around up there?
哦 是的 你指的是美国革命女儿会
Oh, yeah. The Daughters of the Revolution?
就是 可怜的她们都记不起这个老太婆是否
That'd be them. Poor things can't remember if this woman got back
回到了大巴上
on that bus or not.
艾格尼丝 菲尔茨 听说过她吗
Agnes Fields, you hear of her?
没有 我们是刚来不久 所以…
No. Like I said, we just got here, so...
像你们这样可爱的小俩口 在霍布温泉做什么
Just what is a lovely couple like you doing settling in Hobb Springs?
哦 这样的 我们的朋友继承了它
Oh, well, our friend inherited it.
哇 真不错 嗯
Well, nice for him, huh?
听着
Tell you what.
帮我个忙 拿一张去那里给大家看看
You take one of these up there, do me a favor, show it around.
幸运的话 也许有人会认出她
Maybe we get lucky and her face will ring a bell with somebody.
哦 有奖励吗
Oh, is there a reward?
一定 警官
Sure thing, officer.
我无法想象她究竟会出什么事
I can't think what could have happened to her.
- 好 你保重 - 再见
- OK. Well, take care. - See ya.
你们在干嘛
What are you doing?
这个热门玩意在这里不管用
I can't get this hot spot to work.
你们看见丹尼了吗
Have you guys seen Danny?
是的 一分钟前在这里转过
Yeah, he just wandered through here a minute ago.
别管他 让他尽情享受吧
Leave him alone, Mom, he's enjoying himself.
- 有什么不对头吗 - 我不知道
- Something wrong? - I don't know.
- 来吧 我们去找他 - 谢谢
- Come on. Let's go find him. - Thank you.
这地方有点让我毛骨悚然的
I guess this place just gives me the creeps.
丹尼 我们到处在找你
Danny. We've been looking all over for you.
你没事吧
You OK?
来看一下这些相片 我不知道是否该看
Take a look at this picture and tell me if I should be.
那家伙很像丹尼啊
That guy kind of looks like Danny.
甚至有些女人都很像
Even some of the women do.
这个饭店的全部历史都在这了
The whole history of this hotel's up here.
这些人怎么一个也不认识
How could I not know any of these people?
这些相片最近的也是70年代了
These pictures only go up to the '70s.
也许你这边的家族搬走了
Maybe your side of the family moved.
但不是全部 看那张
Not everybody, though. Look.
我想我们看到了你的表兄弟
I think we just met your cousins.
哇哦 伙计们
Whoa, you guys.
为什么他们把自己全罩起来
Why the hell are they all covered up?
这个我可替你破解不了 伙计
I don't know how to break this to you, man,
但是我们在这里看到是典型的山区繁殖
but what we have here is classic mountain breeding.
- 闭嘴 - 我是说 这样的话
- Stop. - I'm just saying, there's bound
一定给后人带来一些缺陷
to be a few defects along the way.
- 真的闭嘴吧 - 你听到没有
- Stop. Seriously. - You heard him!
你觉得我们是山里人 生活方式适应不了现代社会
You think 'cause we're mountain folk, our ways ain't fit for fine society?
我们在这里接待过形形色色的人 包括三位总统
We've had all sorts stay here, including three presidents:
泰迪·罗斯福 卡尔文·柯立芝和杰佛逊·戴维斯
Teddy Roosevelt, Calvin Coolidge, and Jefferson Davis.
没有一个抱怨的
Not one had a complaint!
- 杰佛逊·戴维斯 - 没事了 杰克逊 真的
- Jefferson Davis? - It's OK, Jackson. Really.
他只是在捣乱 是吗 维克
He was just messing around. Weren't you, Vic?
抱歉 我只是为我所继承的感到骄傲
I'm sorry. I'm just very proud of my heritage.
家族的确驯化了这片土地 把它变成了别的东西
Families really tamed this land, they made it into something.
这里非常不错 真的
It's impressive. Really.
是的
Yeah.
想看看真的不错的东西吗
Wanna see something really impressive?
- 好 - 来吧
- Yeah. - Come on.
见鬼
Shit!
- 别去碰 - 抱歉
- Don't touch. - Sorry.
你的眼力很好丹尼 这是你爷爷的
You have a good eye, Danny. It belonged to your grandfather.
- 他精通弓箭 - 这里到处是生物克星啊
- He was hell with a bow. - The bane of critters everywhere.
- 怎么 亲爱的 - 我爷爷
- What is it, honey? - My grandfather.
我的爷爷 我难以相信
My grandfather. I just can't believe I...
甚至还有个爷爷
...even had a grand...
请感觉一下吧
Please. Give it a feel.
哇 那么紧
Man, that's tight.
用箭打过猎吗 丹尼
Ever been bow hunting, Danny?
从来没有
Never been hunting, period.
我宁愿它还是这样保存着
I would like to keep it that way.
小姐 这可不是个好的想法
That's hardly a proper view, miss,
想想你连一次也没试过
considering you haven't even tried it once.
不要啊
Don't.
- 感觉适应吗 - 我正在适应
- Fit OK? - I'm getting used to it.
我知道你会的
I knew you would.
你女朋友 她可真的不愿意让你来
Your girl, she really didn't want you to come.
她只是保护意识 他们都这样
She's just being protective. They all are.
和那个开着豪车带着姑娘的家伙很相称
That guy with the fancy car and girl to match.
布莱恩 我们以前一起共事
Bryan? We used to work together,
在发生… 这一切之前
before it all... happened.
我以前在华尔街干 后来遇到暴跌
I used to be on Wall Street. Had a bit of a meltdown.
- 这样的结果似乎很正常 - 不是人人都这样认为
- Seems an appropriate reaction. - Not everybody thought so.
我的公司不这样认为
Not my company.
绝不是我的客户
Definitely not my clients.
我弄丢了好多人的钱
I lost a lot of people's money.
包括布莱恩的 托妮的 还有我自己的
Including Bryan's, Toni's, my own.
我想那就是你分辨谁才是你真正朋友的时候
I guess that's when you find out who your real friends are.
就是那些愿意支持你的人
The ones who stand by you.
也许他们是觉得你欠了他们的
Maybe they think you owe them.
不 不是他们
No, not them.
那也太让人尴尬了
It was all so embarrassing.
你不适合说那种荒谬的话
You weren't suited to that nonsense.
好的一面来看 那就是我们如何找到你的
On the plus side, it's how we found you.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
我们在这里是有网络可以使用的
We do have the internet out here.
所以你是在谷歌上找到我的
So you found me through Google?
是的 花了好长时间呢 但是找到你对我们说很重要
Yeah. Took a long time. But it was important we found you.
- 来经营旅馆 - 还有其他事情
- To run a hotel? - Amongst other things.
该往上爬了
Time to climb up.
这不是别人的东西吗
This doesn't belong to somebody?
这里所有东西都是属于我们的
Anything on this land belongs to us.
去吧
Go on.
啤酒来了
Beer has arrived.
- 过来吧 伙计 - 靠 我们得去弄个开瓶器
- There you go, dude. - Fuck, we need an opener.
- 是啊 - 嘿 丹尼到哪去了
- Yeah. - Hey! Where's Danny?
出去捕猎了
Out hunting.
- 什么 丹尼吗 - 这是什么
- What, Danny? - What's this?
哦 还记得那几个老太婆吗
Oh, yeah. Remember the little gaggle of old ladies?
- 嗯 - 她们中有一个擅离职守
- Yeah. - Well, one of them went AWOL.
去他的老年痴呆症 伙计 那他妈的跟杀手一样
Fucking Alzheimer's, dude. It's a fucking killer.
- 你得去找一下丹尼 - 现在吗
- You need to go get Danny. - Now?
是的 麻烦了
Yes. Please.
很快就要天黑了
It's gonna get dark soon,
我不想他一个人留下来 跟那些人在一起
and I don't like him alone with these people.
了解 跟老妈似的
OK, Mom.
他们不喜欢你这样哦
They ain't gonna like it.
- 你确定我们不要 - 嘘…
- Are you sure we don't... - Sh!
需要许可什么的
...need a permit or anything?
每一个人都有他自己的生活原刚
Every man lives by his own set of rules.
说到这个 我该教你怎么捕猎了
Speaking of which, time to introduce you to the hunt.
第一步 你要侦查一下 然后延伸开来去找
First you gotta scout, then stretch.
鹿会觉得安全的地方
Someplace the deer feels safe.
那些人们到不了的地方
Where men can't get to it.
在你的区域设诱饵
Bait your area.
用你的方式引诱鹿
Lure, entice the deer over your ways.
不要去追赶你的猎物
You don't wanna go after your prey.
而是要让你的猎物自己送上门来
You let your prey come to you.
这就是耐心的问题了
It's about patience.
你要比那些动物聪明
And being smarter than the animal.
别动
Be still.
瞄准它们肩部以上的部位
Aim for the upper shoulder.
颈部
The neck.
或者头部
Or the brain.
一次瞄准 射击到位
A one-shot kill.
现在我们要来查看一下流血的痕迹
Now we check the blood trail.
带着气泡的粉色血液代表着
Pink blood with air bubbles means
你射中了它的心脏或者是肺部
you've hit the heart or the lung.
现在是你要的
Now that's what you want.
血呈暗红 你可能是射中了它的肝脏
Dark red, you probably hit the liver.
雄鹿会挺一段时间 但是过一会它们就会挂了
Yhe buck may hang in there, but they will die soon enough.
血色很淡的还带了点胆汁的 你就得去追踪它们
Watery blood with bile, you may have to track the deer,
然后再射一次
deliver another shot.
它可能会想要冲出去
He may try to bolt.
但是如果你己经瞄准了 那正好有了反作用力
But if you've aimed just right, it'll be pure reflex.
射得很好 丹尼
Good shot, Danny.
- 接下来要做什么 - 没有了
- What do we do next? - Nothing.
是暗红色的血 它很快就会死
It's dark red blood. Besides, he'll be dead soon.
我们有太多的肉能拿回去了 快走吧
We have more than enough meat back home. Come on.
我们不能就这样离开
We can't just leave it like this.
你来杀了它
It's your kill.
小心点
Just be careful.
它可能会用后腿反踢
He may have some kick left in him.
肩部以上的部位 颈部或者是脑部 去吧
Upper shoulder, neck or brain. Go.
做得很好 丹尼
Very good, Danny.
很好
That's very good.
查理 你对着那堆干草做什么呢
Charlie, what did you do to this weed?
哦 我靠
Oh, fuck this!
见鬼
Shit!
天哪
Jesus!
- 你在流血 - 你也是
- You're bleeding. - So are you.
无论如何大多数血都不是我的 啊
Most of it's not mine anyway. Ah!
我们得离开这里 他看到我的脸了
We've gotta get out of here! He saw my face.
- 谁 你绊倒了吗 - 没有 我没有
- Who? Are you tripping? - Not anymore, I'm not.
- 这可真乱啊 - 啊啊啊
- This is fucked up! - Ahh!
- 是他 - 放松一点 也可能只是杰克森
- It's him. - Relax. It's probably just Jackson.
或许不是呢 就是这边 从末端拉 慢点 慢点
Or not. Here, pull from that end. Pull from that. Slow, slow, slow!
弄不下来啊 这都拧在一起了
It's not coming! It's too twisted!
- 去找人帮忙 - 我不能丢下你
- Go get some help! - I can't leave you!
- 快去 - 好吧
- Go! - OK.
啊
Ah!
对不起 弄疼你了 亲爱的
Sorry if it stings, sweetie.
没有 没有 那没关系的
No, no, it's OK.
我也在为那个事情责怪维克
I'm blaming Vic for that too.
你应该在这个森林里很有把握的
You have to be sure about these woods.
我听到雄鹿的声音 你第一次开枪
So I heard a buck, your first time shooting.
那并不是雄鹿
It wasn't a buck.
- 我杀了一只母鹿 - 那不是更好吗
- I killed a doe. - Even better.
- 是很猛烈的药膏吗 - 是的
- Is that strong stuff? - Yeah.
- 它闻起来是那样的 - 是啊
- It sure smells like it. - Yeah.
- 你需要习惯一下 - 不不不 没 没事的 真的
- It takes some getting used to. - No, no, it's... it's fine, actually.
我挺喜欢的
I kinda like it.
我自己一个人做到了
I do make it myself.
你到那里坐
You sit right there.
我很快就回来 我得去把我手上这些东西洗掉
We'll be right back. I'm gonna wash this off of my hands.
现在把这些血弄掉吧
Now to get you out of those bloody things.
没事的 我自己可以搞定
All right, it's OK. I can do it.
不要那样 我可是帮我所有的兄弟们
Now, don't you be that way. I patched up all my brothers
都处理过伤口的
one time or another.
好吧
OK. Fine.
你们男人都是那种反应
All you boys react that way.
我想说你真的好强壮
I'd say you're strong enough.
你…
You just...
你还有些伤口要擦
You just have some aches that need rubbing out.
托妮一会就会来这儿 所以…
Toni will be here any second, so...
不必再等了
There's no sense waiting.
你对我们来说很重要
You're very important to us.
你甚至都不了解我
You don't even know me.
但是我是知道的
But I know this.
我们俩都对对方动心了
And it beats inside every one of us.
你的理智 你的教育 你的力量
And with your mind, your schooling, your strength,
还有你的血液
and our blood,
你可以得到一切你想要的
you can have anything you want.
- 我还是觉得那很难相信 - 你不要
- I still find it hard to believe that. - Don't you?
额 这…
What's, uh...
你刚刚去哪里了
Where have you been?
杰克森让我照顾丹尼
Jackson brought Danny to me to tend to.
我感觉有点混乱啊 亲爱的
I got pretty messed up, hon.
是啊 维克看起来好像也不怎么好
Yeah, Vic didn't look so good either.
我得去照顾他了
I should go tend to him.
你觉得她也要去帮维克 把衣服脱掉
Think she's gonna help Vic take off his clothes too?
哦 别这样 别这么说 她刚刚只是想要帮忙
Oh, come on, stop. She was just trying to help.
很明显 她只是帮她自己
Help herself, obviously.
你看起来好严重
You look gross.
疼吗 哦
Does it hurt? Oh!
- 你腿上那层是什么 - 哦 是药膏
- What is all over your legs? - Oh, it's ointment.
是家庭配方
It's a family formula.
天哪 你要感染了 你得躺下
God, you're gonna get infected. You should lay down.
- 现在你说话吧 - 啊 别摸我
- Now you're talking. - Ew! Don't touch me!
- 嘿 别这样 - 不要 不要摸我
- Hey, come on. Come on. - Don't! Don't touch me.
- 你真让人恶心 不 - 求你了 过来啊
- You're disgusting. No. - Please. Come here.
这不是… 过氧化氢在哪里呢
It's not... where's the peroxide?
我对这感觉很不好
I had a bad feeling about this.
你拿开吧
You going.
你真的杀了什么东西吗
Did you actually kill something?
因为看起来你好像在血泊之中滚动
Because it looks like you rolled around in blood.
是啊 我拿着弓箭
Yeah, with a bow and arrow.
- 你真的 - 是的
- You actually... - Yeah.
那真酷啊 嗯
It's pretty cool, huh?
- 不 - 是的 那很酷的
- No! - Yeah, it is.
不 不是的 我没觉得印象深刻
No, it's not. I'm not impressed.
- 过来 - 你现在是什么人呢 猎人吗
- Come here. - What are you, a hunter now?
哦 是啊 很大的成功 伟大的人 伟大的猎人
Oh, yeah, big time. Big man. Big man hunter.
我们也该打猎了
We should pick up hunting.
- 为什么那么阴郁啊 甜心 - 别拍我
- Why so glum, sugarplum? - Get that thing out of my face.
我可以用植原草本让你提起兴趣吗
Can I interest you in an herbal essence?
把那东西拿走 离我远点
Keep that shit away from me too.
你看见了山里的野人 你逃了
You see one mountain monster man, and you go cold turkey.
- 我看见了… - 什么
- I saw... - What?
没什么 把那个给我
Nothing. Give that to me.
- 你伙计 - 哦 拍一下
- You. Dude! - Oh, shoot!
你们知道今天看到什么了吗 内战时代
You know what I saw today? Civil War era.
刀叉匙 银制的
Flatware. Silver.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
哦 你知道的 今晚来感受一下爱
Oh, you know. Just feeling some love tonight.
现在 来吧 来吧 嚓嚓
Now. Go, go, chug!
开始吧 开始吧
There we go, there we go.
就是这样 是啊
There it is! Yeah!
给我一下
Give that.
- 嘿 伙计 - 啊
- Hey, man. - Ah!
- 很好 - 你现在看到野人了吗 啊
- Nice. - You see any mountain men now? Ahh!
没有
No.
好多了
Better.
- 等一下 - 那是什么
- Wait. - What is it?
- 现在我感觉好多了 - 该死
- Now I feel better. - Damn it!
快点 吉尔 给我们展示一下狂野的女孩
Come on, Jill! Give us the old Girls Gone Wild.
去你的 我比较想看你们几个疯狂的样子
Fuck you! I'd like to see you guys do Boys Gone Wild.
什么意思
What do you mean?
- 现在 这是一个派对啦 - 拿开那个
- Now it's a party! - Get that away!
真讨厌 你们太讨厌了
Sick. You're sick.
- 来吧 伙计们 - 对不起
- Come on, guys. - Sorry.
- 耶 - 很好
- Yeah! - Nice!
伙计们 舞动起来
Show us the moves, guys.
哇
Whoa!
你还好吗 伙计
You OK, man?
等一下 你在做什么呢
Wait a second. You're doing what?
恢复霍布温泉庄园 从上到下
Restoring Hobb Springs. Top to bottom.
我们明年夏天就可以有一个 盛大的重新开业啦
Figure we could have a grand reopening by next summer.
你们昨天晚上做什么了
What did you do to him last night?
- 不是我 - 是我的主意
- This isn't me. - It was my decision.
这个地方有点事
There's something about this place.
你们刚到这里来的时候 有没有觉得什么不一样
Haven't you guys felt different since you got here?
- 是啊 我处于极度兴奋中 - 在这里昏倒
- Yeah. I've been freaking out. - Passing out over here.
- 托妮 - 不 我们因为你很开心
- Toni? - No, we're really happy for you, hon.
- 但是这个地方 - 很棒 还能再来一次
- But this place... - Was great. And it can be again.
你们知道关于经营旅馆 或是温泉的一些东西吗
Do you even know anything about... about running a hotel, or a spa?
我不是仅仅为了钱去做的
I'm not just doing it for the money.
我们知道 我们真的知道
No, we get that. We really do.
罗德 你说过我们已经做好了很棒的网络系统
Rod? You said that we'd all make a great web series.
还有什么能比拍摄一伙朋友 重建里程碑更好的了吗
What better way to film a group of friends restoring a great landmark.
是哦 当然 能把那些拍摄的录像剪辑到一起
Yeah. I could definitely cut a good sizzle reel together.
- 把它做成一个土里土气的真实世界 - 维克 你呢
- Make it a rustic Real World. - And Vic?
你说过要写一本关于这个地方的书的
You said you were game for writing a book about the history of this place.
- 没错 但是… - 看到了吗 布里
- Sure, but... - See, Bry?
我们建造了意识
We build awareness.
剩下的只是简单的商业意识
The rest of it is just simple business sense
那就是为什么他们要给我们一大笔钱
and that's why they paid us the big bucks.
你想说什么呢 伙计
What do you say, man?
好吧 我觉得草拟一个商业计划 不会有什么坏处的
Well, I guess it wouldn't hurt to draw up a business plan.
我知道 你又要来了
I knew you'd come around.
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
那你为什么还要我说呢
Then why are you gonna make me say it?
你看见那小子了吗 整天的
Did you look at the guy? It's like night and day.
我们应该回到城里
We were supposed to be going back to the city.
我不是那么容易就能回去的 你知道
It's not so easy for me to just pack it all in, you know.
我们是来帮助他的
We came here to help him.
我甚至不知道我们为什么还是他的朋友
I don't even know why we're still friends with the guy!
哦 天哪 你就是不知道什么时候闭嘴
Oh, my God! You just don't know when to shut up!
这是什么
What?
你到底干了什么
What exactly were you doing with that?
吉莉安
Jillian?
这是斯塔福德郡
This is Staffordshire.
你知道这些值多少钱
Do you have any idea how much these are worth?
多少
How much?
最少2000
Two thousand, at least.
屋子里装满了 我…
Cabinet's full of them. I...
我想没有人会注意到
I didn't think anyone would notice.
让我看看
Show me.
你还发现哪里有这东西
Where else have you checked for these?
就这 我不想自己看
Just here. I didn't wanna look alone.
好吧 我把它们给你拿来 你编个目录 好吗
All right. I'll bring them to you, and you catalogue them. OK?
好
Yes!
嘿
Hey.
哦 对
Oh, yeah.
这个… 真美
These... are perfect.
真的有秘道
So secret passages really do exist.
是哦 但是往哪里呢
Yeah, but where do they lead?
检查一下那些柜子
Check out those cupboards.
我们要下去吗
Are we going down there?
他们把无价的古董摆在外边
They keep priceless antiques out in the open.
你能想象他们要隐藏什么吗
Can you imagine what they decided to hide?
- 嘿 他们… - 对
- Hey. Are they... - Yep.
他们正在干
They're screwing.
那他妈是什么
What the hell is that?
我想我知道
I think I know.
明白了吗
Get the idea?
等一下
Wait.
你说他们在这做爱
You're saying that they would just have sex here
- 其他人站在一边看 - 嗯哼
- while people stood by and watched? - Mm-hm.
天啊 这是一个古怪的温泉浴场
Geez. This is one kinky spa.
哇 哇
Whoa, whoa!
- 你干什么 - 我同意你的说法
- What are you doing? - Well, I'm agreeing with you.
古怪的 是吗
Kinky, right?
等等 你真的想要干这个
Wait. Are we really gonna do this?
是的
Yeah.
不
No!
停下
Stop!
你们应该等等
You were supposed to wait!
现在你们亵渎了这屋子
Now you disrespect this room?
好 现在滚吧
Well, go on now!
你们应该回到你们的地方去
You might as well take what you came for.
把他给我留下
He stays with me.
滚
Get!
看那些小子们把你打的…
What those boys did to you...
你喜欢这个
You like that?
你的头伤得真的很厉害
Your head's hurt real bad.
但是我看见过人活得更糟糕
But I've seen people live with a lot worse.
就让萨莉照顾你吧
Just let Sally take care of you.
你真美
You're so handsome.
我想你喜欢我蹭来蹭去的
I think you like me rubbing up against you.
不…
No...
我可以比那个婊子干得让你更舒服
I can make you feel better than that stuck-up bitch you brought.
萨莉
Sally!
你应该保持体力等着
You're supposed to be saving yourself for when the time's right.
什么时候开始
When's that gonna be?
我知道很难等
I know it's hard to wait.
但是我很近了 我可以摸到他
But I'm so close, that I can touch him.
这个人怎么进来的
How did this one get in here to begin with?
我试过阻止他们
I tried to stop 'em.
事实上让他们停止是个小奇迹
The fact they stopped at all is a small miracle.
- 他们就是不听话 - 那就今夜
- They're just not listening. - Tonight then.
我们让他们今夜见到丹尼
We have them all meet Danny tonight.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
干掉他
Finish him off.
带他去厨房
Take him to the kitchen.
我一会把他埋了
We'll carve him up later.
别担心 宝贝
Don't you fret, lover.
你会和我在一起 不管是什么形式
You'll be in me, one way or another.
水管坏了
Water damage.
故障管线
Fried outlets.
发霉了
Mold.
我需要更多的照片
I'm gonna need some more paper.
如果我们知道丹尼想什么 会相当快的
This would go a hell of a lot faster if we knew what Danny had in mind.
丹尼去哪了
Where is Danny?
我们需要找到这些地方的核心
We need keys to some of these places.
看看前面的桌子
Check the front desk.
只有当星期三亚当斯休息的时候
Only if Wednesday Adams is on a break.
- 维克 - 好的
- Vic. - Fine.
我走 但是你要去找你的男朋友 这都是他的主意
I'll go, but you go get your boyfriend. This was all his idea.
丹尼
Danny?
托妮 嘿
Toni! Hey.
我们可以用小指导出去 拜托
We could all use a little guidance out there, please.
好
OK.
- 这都是你干的吗 - 不是
- Did you do all this? - No.
- 这是吉利安的 - 是的
- This is Jillian's. - Yeah.
她是想要拿走这些
Was she trying to take these?
我不知道
I don't know.
她和布里经常去甩货
She and Bry were always going on about selling things off.
没问过你吗
Without asking you?
说到钱 布莱恩做得糟糕
When it comes to money, Bryan's done worse.
- 你在哪看到过他们吗 - 没有
- Have you seen them anywhere? - No.
看起来他们带走了一些离别礼物
Looks like they took off with a few parting gifts.
虽然这不像是他们的所作所为
That's not like them, though.
嗯 我猜你从不曾真正了解任何人 哈
Well, I guess you never really know anybody, huh?
三年来我们都不曾了解他们
We've known them for three years.
是的 他们简单又粗爆
Yeah, all they've ever been about is the quick and easy.
布莱恩和他的次贷
Bryan with his subprimes,
吉利安扮演着她的曼哈顿上流婊子
and Jillian playing the Manhattan socialite bitch.
- 丹尼 - 她来自威斯康辛州
- Danny! - She's from Wisconsin.
我的意思是 我给了他们上来的机会
I mean, I gave 'em a chance to get in on the ground floor.
人们自己努力 上帝也不会给机会让他们成功
God forbid they ever achieve anything in life by actually working for it.
- 这是我在这里努力要做的事 - 哇哦 丹尼
- That's what I'm trying to do here. - Wow, Danny.
- 他们是你的朋友 - 你知道为什么布莱恩如此渴望
- They are your friends. - You know why Bryan's so eager
在公司的时候让我回去
to get me back in the firm?
所以他不必做任何的工作
So he didn't have to do any work.
我总能得到更大的提升 看到我付出什么
I always did the heavy lifting, and look what that cost me.
它们是我过去的生活… 这是我现在的生活
They're my old life. This... this is my new one.
我的天 我现在真的非常努力地变得有能力
My God! I am really trying hard to be supportive right now,
但是我唯一不想知道的就是你
but the only person I don't feel like I know is you!
- 你在说什么啊 - 就是这里
- What are you talking about? - It is this place!
- 你想把我带到这里来 - 因为我以为这样会有帮助
- You wanted to bring me here. - Because I thought it was gonna help.
确实有 萨莉都发现了异样
And it has! Even Sally noticed the difference
- 从我来这里的时候 - 噢 我的天 萨莉
- from when I got here. - Oh, my God. Sally?
- 噢 不要再说了 - 你想把 不不 不
- Oh, don't start that again. - You wanna bring up... No, no! No!
她和她的兄弟/老公/表亲/无论是啥
Her and her brother/husband/cousin/whatever.
- 够了 妈的 - 他们是唯一
- Enough of that shit! - They are the only ones
我们不知道关于他们的一切 你怎么就不明白
that we really know nothing about! How do you not get that?
你想知道 自己去问他们
You wanna know something? Go ask them yourself.
是的 你有吗 你查证过
Yeah, have you? Have you checked into
他们告诉你的一切吗
anything that they've told you?
- 他们只是对我很好 - 难道没有
- They have been nothing but kind to me. - And we haven't?
- 你不懂 - 哦 我的
- You don't understand. - Oh, my...
- 这些人是我 - 什么 他们是什么
- These people are my... - What?! What are they?!
你知道吗 你从来就不知道 丹尼
Do you even know? You don't even know, Danny!
去你妈的
Fuck you!
你们明白吗
Did you get all that?
好了 没事 没事了
Look, it's OK. It's OK.
- 杰克森 萨莉 - 这里 丹尼
- Jackson? Sally? - In here, Danny.
- 我得和你们谈谈 - 我们会和你在一起
- I need to talk to you. - And we with you.
我们有太多事情需要解释了 我们不确定到底是怎么回事
There's so many things we need to explain, we're just not sure how.
我知道这对你来说太震撼了
I'm sure this is already so overwhelming for you.
- 你再说一遍 - 我们很高兴你们
- You could say that again. - And we're thrilled that you're
- 对这家宾馆感兴趣 - 但是已经
- interested in the hotel. - But it's already
这只是关于我们是谁的一小方面
just such a small aspect of who we really are.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我想我们告诉你的话会比较好
I think it's better if we show you.
但你得一个人来
But you gotta come alone.
你的家人见到你会很满足的
There's members of the family that have been aching to meet you.
- 走吧 - 来吧
- Let's go. - Come on.
用手电简不是更方便吗
Wouldn't it be easier to use a flashlight?
我们都是这样的
It's the way we do things.
你会知道的
You'll see.
- 这些人是谁 - 他们都是亲戚
- Who are all these people? - They're all kin,
怎么办
one way or another.
欢迎你回家 丹尼
Come to welcome you home, Danny.
你做这个多久了
How long have you been doing this?
从我们家族第一次踏上这片山丘的时候相识
We've known each other since our clans first set foot in these hills.
那些天有三个家族回来了
There were three families back in those days.
柯瑞顿 鲍格斯和希里克
The Craytons, the Boggles and the Hillickers.
- 我是哪一个的 - 你是希里克家族的 丹尼
- Which am I? - You're Hillicker, Danny.
- 还有你们呢 - 我们是血亲
- And all of you? - We're blood.
是啊
Yeah.
我们的家族征服了这片土地
Our families tamed this land.
获得了这里的回报 煤炭和木材
Reaped its rewards, the coal, the timber.
其他人想夺走我们获取的东西
Others tried to chisel in on what we'd earned,
但这是我们与生俱来的
but we had birthright.
这个给女士 这个给你
That's for the lady. That's for you.
- 这是什么 - 家族红酒
- What's that? - It's the family vintage.
看 就像红酒一样 霍布温泉是一种家族的传承
See, like this brew, Hobb Springs is a testament to family.
这是我们四面八方的人聚集的地方
It's a place for our folk to gather from far and wide.
和他们一起来的人
With them came others.
就像和你一起来的朋友
Like your friends came with you.
他们带着诱饵到处流浪
And they bring temptation to stray.
削弱我们的家族 弄脏我们的血液
Weakened our family, muddied our blood.
看着 你怎样维持家族的力量
See, how do you preserve family strength?
你怎样使它一尘不染
How do you keep it pure?
怎样
How?
我们可以坚守自己
We stick to our own.
这没什么好怕的 亲爱的 没什么好怕的
There's nothing to fear, sweetie. There's nothing to fear.
- 你们怎么了 - 纯洁的代价
- What happened to them? - It's the price of purity.
纯洁…
Purity...
坚守住我们自己
Stick to our own...
那是对的 丹尼 家族 叔叔 表亲
That's right, Danny. Family. Uncle, cousin.
兄弟
Brother.
看 传统已经成为了一种仪式
See, what was tradition became ritual.
这种仪式保留了我们的血统 甚至清除了它
And that ritual preserved our blood lines, it cleansed it even.
我们的贡献是强大的 但是当它被削弱的时候…
Our devotion was strong and rewarded, but when it was weak...
我们会得到惩罚
...we were punished.
因此这是一代人
So it's been for generations.
- 后来一切都变坏了 - 没有孩子再参与进来
- Lately, everything has gone wrong. - No child comes to terms.
要是那样 他们无法生存
The ones that do, they don't survive.
- 这就是我们为什么需要你 丹尼 - 为什么
- And that's why we need you, Danny. - Why?
看着 只有纯正的血统才能 维持这个家族的生存
See, only true blood will keep this family alive.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
丹尼 你和我
Danny, you and me.
我们的血液一直是纯正的
Our blood is still true.
它们本该在一起
It belongs together.
妈的
Get the... Fuck!
啊
Ah!
滚开
Get the fuck off!
丹尼
Danny!
- 丹尼 - 我认识他
- Danny! - I know him.
不 你想多了
No. You only think you do.
丹尼
Danny!
啊 该死的
Ah! What the fuck?!
对不起 我 我不认识你
I'm sorry, I... I don't know who you are.
新鲜的生命
Flesh is life.
长生不老
Long life.
丹尼
Danny!
- 各位 - 噢
- Guys. - Oh!
夫哪 托妮
Jesus, Toni.
- 也许是丹尼或维克 - 快来
- Maybe it's Danny or Vic. - Come on.
这个 托妮 退回去
Here. Toni, stay back.
准备 数三下
Ready? On three.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
- 噢 该死 - 他妈的
- Oh, shit! - Fuck!
我说 老兄 我们差点杀了你
I'll say, we almost killed you, man!
丹尼 你怎么了
Danny! What the hell happened to you?
- 呃 - 什么…
- Huh? - Wha...
- 发生什么事情 - 我在喝酒
- What happened? - I was drinking.
- 喝很多 - 喝酒
- A lot. - Drinking?
在跳舞
There was dancing.
- 搞烧烤 - 噢 耶 听起来很好的样子
- Had a barbeque. - Oh, yeah, sounds nice. Yeah.
我们 我们不敢睡了
Us? We were scared out of a sound sleep
被一群疯子放肆地敲门
by some maniac banging on the fucking door!
喔喔喔 冷静点
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Calm down.
我现在不想听这个 好吗 罗德
I don't need this right now, Rod. OK?
丹尼… 这些是抓痕吗
Danny... are these scratches?
我不知道 你应该知道的 哈 达 达
I don't know. You should know, huh? Da, da...
- 停停 - 嘿 拜托 老兄
- Stop. Stop. - Hey, come on, dude.
- 丹尼 - 拜托 起开 拜托
- Danny. - Come on, get off. Come on.
- 好的 好的 - 我们得马上走
- All right, all right. - Listen, we need to leave right now.
该死 我到家了
Fuck that. I'm home.
这不是你家
This is not your home.
你知道什么 你们可以走了
You know what? You guys can leave.
布莱恩和吉利安 他们走了
Bryan and Jillian, they did.
- 维克走了 - 什么
- Vic did. - What?
- 维克走了 - 维克怎么了
- Vic left? - Danny, what happened to Vic?
我怎么知道
How the fuck should I know?
- 想走吗 - 别
- Wanna go? - Stop!
- 拜托 - 别
- Come on! - Don't!
你们知道什么 伙计们 我
You know what, guys? I'm...
可不可以让我好好睡会 拜托
Why don't you just let me get some sleep, please.
伙计们 我从来没有看他这么糟糕
Guys, I've never seen him this fucked up.
- 是的 - 你们可以扶他上楼吗
- No. - Should you guys carry him upstairs
- 或做点什么 - 耶 维克怎么了
- or something? - Yeah, but what about Vic?
我不知道
I don't know.
你们闻到了吗
Do you guys smell that?
- 等等 - 查理
- Hold on. - Charlie!
噢 他妈的
Oh, fuck.
走 走
Go, go!
我们得弄走丹尼
We have to get Danny to go.
不管他愿不愿意
Whether he wants to or not.
起来 查理 走
Get up, Charlie! Go!
托妮 走
Toni, go!
把托妮带走 快
Get Toni out of here right now!
快走
Go now!
啊
Ahh!
噢
Oh!
他在哪里 罗德 我们得找到他
Where is he, Rod? We have to find him!
不 我们先走 再带人来
No! We go and come back for help!
- 我们不能丢下他 - 他想留下来
- We can't leave him here! - He wants to stay!
你不懂吗 我想他清楚目前的情况
Don't you get that?! I think he knows what's been going on!
不 不
No! No!
当你问维克的事时 你都看见了
You saw when you asked about Vic.
不 丹尼不会做这些事的 罗德 丹尼不会那样
No. Danny would never do that, Rod! Danny would never do that!
- 听着 你哥变了 - 不
- Listen to your brother for a change! - No!
托妮 托妮
Toni! Toni!
该死
Shit!
托妮
Toni?
- 求你别开枪 - 丹尼在哪
- Please don't shoot me. - Where's Danny?
丹尼在哪
Where is Danny?!
- 他在属于他的地方 - 你们对他做了什么
- Where he belongs. - What did you do to him?
- 你们做了什么 - 他喜欢那样
- Did you do something to him? - But he liked it.
他不知道你是谁 我知道
He doesn't know what you are. I do.
我知道
I do!
所以现在你认为你知道我们的秘密
So you think you know all of our secrets now?
你们就是凶手
You're murderers!
你们吃人
You eat people!
你不审判我吗
Don't you judge me.
我会告诉丹尼所有关于你的事
I'm gonna tell Danny everything about you.
他知道的
He knows.
所以他留下了
That's why he's staying.
和我配种
To fill me with a baby.
我能感觉婴儿要出生了
And I can already feel that baby coming deep inside.
噢
Oh!
你该得的 婊子
You're gonna get yours now, girl!
你想试试开水在你脸上灼烧的感觉吗
You wanna see what firewater does to that pretty face?!
噢
Ah!
不
No!
你在做什么
What the hell are you doing?!
噢 天哪 萨莉
Oh, my God, Sally.
没事的 萨莉…
It's OK. Sh, sh...
- 你在杀我的家人 - 家人
- You're trying to kill my family now? - Family?
我们才是你的家人 丹尼… 他们所杀的
We're your family, Danny. The ones they killed.
我要你走的
I told you to leave!
你不走我不走
Not without you.
你已经不了解我了 我已经不是从前的我了
You don't know me anymore. I've changed.
而且你也不属于这里 所以在你没受伤之前 快离开
And you don't belong here. So just go before you get hurt!
受伤
Hurt?
就像维克吗
Like Vic?!
就像布莱恩和吉利安一样 是吗 丹尼
Like Bryan and Jillian, Danny?!
受伤 他们不是受伤了 是死了
Hurt?! They're not hurt! They're dead!
快滚
Just fucking leave!
你伤害我妹妹
You fucking hurt my sister. Huh?!
够了 够了
Enough! Enough.
- 我说停下 - 哦 不
- I said stop! - Oh, no.
恐怕我不能听你的 丹尼 她知道得太多了
I'm afraid I can't do that, Danny. She knows an awful lot.
没人会相信她的话 这点她明白
No one will believe her. She knows that.
- 哦 不能就这么放过她 - 你还有我
- Oh! That is not enough! - You have me.
我现在是希里克 你不需要她了
I'm a Hillicker now. You don't need her too.
非常抱歉
I'm really sorry.
你知道的 我们有一套自己的办事方式
You see, we have our ways.
别担心 宝贝 我下手很快的
Don't worry, baby, I'm gonna make this real quick.
让我来
I'll do it.
- 什么 - 我说让我来
- What? - I said I'll do it.
我把她带来的 我来解决她
I brought her here, and she's my responsibility.
- 那你来 - 不
- You do it. - No!
动作快点
Make it fucking quick!
不 不
No! No!
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
不 不 不 不
No! No! No! No!
你太拖沓了 丹尼
You're taking too long, Danny.
- 快跑 - 快干掉她
- Run. - Fucking finish her!
别回头
And don't look back.
你他妈的…
You fucking...
丹尼 不
Danny, no.
我给你说过 快走
I told you to leave.
- 我试着跑过了 - 你不听
- I tried. - You didn't listen.
我做不到
I couldn't.
- 现在你杀了我们中的一个 - 我不杀他 我就会死
- Now you've gone and killed one of us. - He was trying to kill me.
- 我不会杀你们的 - 我帮不了你了
- This isn't happening. - I can't help you anymore.
别这样 丹尼 你不是这种人
Just stop, Danny! This isn't you!
不
No.
我们是一家人
It's family.
祝你愉快 谢谢
You have a fantastic day, thank you.
嘿 伙计们 还好吗 这地方怎样
Hey, guys, how are you? Find the place OK?
欢迎来到希里克温泉庄园
Welcome to Hillicker Springs.
多呆一段时间 体验下我们的温泉
Just you wait until you've experienced our hot springs.
试一次死了都值了
Boy, are they to die for.
现在我带你们去房间
Now, go find your rooms, OK?
祝你们住得愉快
Enjoy your stay.
反正我会愉快
I know I will.
女士你好 嗨
How are you ladies? Hi.
嘿 你好 觉得我们的全蛋白自助餐怎么样啊
Hey, how are you? You enjoying our all-protein buffet?
- 我已经减掉了6磅 - 哇哦
- I've already lost six pounds. - Wow!
继续坚持哦
Don't go disappearing on us now, OK?
各位 我们有更重要的工作要做了
Come on, boys, we've got more important work to do, huh?
来 快 快
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
快点
Come on.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们会一直尝试
We'll keep trying and trying.
不是那样的
It's not that.
那是什么样的
What then, sweetie?
我就是很高兴
I'm just happy.